deletemalware.blogspot.com 2011-10-06

# Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us. If you give us personal information, we treat it according to the [Google Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacy.html). We do not otherwise share it. 

**What Information Do We Collect?**  
In order to post comments on deletemalware.blogspot.com, you may be asked to enter your name and e-mail address. You may, however, post comments anonymously. Comments are moderated and any bad links will be removed. E-mail or any other personal contact information (AIM, OpenID, Facebook) may be used to pass further information to you with your consent or if you have specifically asked for further assistance. 

**What do we use your information for?**  
We use personal information to improve deletemalware.blogspot.com. We customize our blog’s content and layout to better tailor it to meet users' needs.

**Do We Use Cookies?**  
Yes. For more information, please read [Google Privacy FAQ](http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacy/faq.html#toc-cookies)

**Advertising and Privacy**  
The ads appearing on this blog are delivered to readers by Google AdSense. For more information, please read [Google Advertising Cookie and Privacy Policies](http://www.google.com/support/adsense/bin/answer.py?hl=en&answer=100557).

**Links to Other Websites**  
This blog contains links to other websites that are not owned and controlled by deletemalware.blogspot.com. Please be aware that these third party websites have separate privacy policies and we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other websites. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this blog. 

**Your Consent**  
By using deletemalware.blogspot.com, you consent to this privacy policy. 

**Changes in This Privacy Policy**  
We may change this privacy policy from time to time. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement. 

This privacy policy was last modified on 03/07/2011

**Contacting Us**  
If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy or blog you can email us at [kaur.michael@gmail.com](mailto:kaur.michael@gmail.com). You can also leave a comment at the bottom of any post on this blog.
